Shawn Rhodes

Front End Developer & Web Designer

shawn@massivelines.com

501-733-9480

https://massivelines.github.io/

Summary

- Proven leader and team player with a strong record of exceeding goals and expectations.
- Skilled in front-end development using multiple scripting tools and languages, and a drive to learn new processes and design techniques.
- Experienced in an array of multimedia tools and design approaches including typography, visual arts, and page layout.

<u>Interests</u>

Sports Cars (Nissan 370Z), Video Games (PUBG and Rocket League), Craft Beer (primarily bourbon barrel aged), Photography (panoramic landscapes), Physical Art (letterpress and screen print)

Skills

<u>Core</u>	<u>Javascript</u>	<u>Frameworks</u>	<u>CSS</u>	<u>Design</u>	<u>Other</u>
HTML5	Bootstrap	jQuery	Sass	Photoshop	git
CSS3	Foundation	Node	Less	Illustrator	GitHub
Javascript	Wordpress	React		XD	Heroku
		Electron			

Education & Certifications

University of Texas at Dallas

University of Arkansas Community College-Morrilton

Grow With Google Scholarship	January 2018 to March 2018
Front End Web Development	

Front End Development Certificate	March 2017 to June 2017
freeCodeCamp	

Bachelor of Arts: Art and Technology	August 2011 to December 2014
Animation and Graphic Design	

General Credits	August 2007 to December 2008
University of Arkansas at Little Rock	

Associate of Applied Science	January 2004 to August 2005
Automotive Design, Color, and Refinishing	

Employment

Independent Contractor	October 2015 to Current
Self Employed – Dallas Tx	

Department Manager	March 2004 to October 2015
Walmart - Plano Ty	